Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Collection, Part II: Field Recordings AIA.031.002
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series II: Non-digitized Tapes, 1956-2001
  - II:B Public Recordings
    - "Chicago Session: Tom Ward's etc. and Interview with Jimmy and Eleanor Neary." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], May 2, 1980 (Box 19, Item aiamm536R)
    - Nashville Concert. Concert performance by Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo) and Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) in Nashville, TN. (Length: 01:30:00), May 10, 1980 (Box 25, Item aiamm921C)
    - "Philadelphia: Tony O'Sullivan, Kevin Barnard, Timmy Britton, Mark Simos." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], Jul 14, 1980 (Box 27, Item aiamm922C)
    - Port Townsend Session. Session in Washington state with Moloney and Billy McComiskey (accordion). (Length: 01:30:00), Aug 30, 1980 (Box 25, Item aiamm923C)
    - "Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival - Fiddle Workshop." Musicians include Liz Carroll and Johnny McGreevy. [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], Sep, 1980 (Box 27, Item aiamm924C)
    - McMahon, Tony (accordion), Moloney, Mick (guitar, vocals) Concert performance on McMahon's first trip to America at the Eagle Tavern, New York, NY. (Part one of two) (Length:01:00:00), Oct 29, 1980 (Box 26, Item aiamm925C)
    - McMahon, Tony (accordion), Moloney, Mick (guitar, vocals) Concert performance on McMahon's first trip to America at the Eagle Tavern, New York, NY. (Part two of two) (Length:00:15:00), Oct 29, 1980 (Box 26, Item aiamm926C)
    - Irish Tradition (group) Pub concert performance by Billy McComiskey (accordion), Brendan Mulvihill (fiddle), Andy O'Brien (guitar, vocals) at Tom O'Reilly's Pub. (Length: 01:30:00), Oct, 1980 (Box 26, Item aiamm927C)
    - "Ballisodare Folk Festival II." Concert performances by Stockton's Wing, Paul Brady, Ossian and Jimmy Crowley. (Length: 01:30:00), circa 1980 (Box 26, Item aiamm928C)
    - Philadelphia Ceili Group Spring Concert - "Tape 1." Concert performances in Philadelphia, PA from Maureen Fitzpatrick (fiddle), Brian Conway (fiddle), Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Andy McGann (fiddle), Joe Burke (accordion), Lori Cole (piano). Tape plays back too fast. (Length: 01:30:00), 1981 (Box 26, Item aiamm929C)
    - Philadelphia Ceili Group Spring Concert - "Tape 2." Concert performances in Philadelphia, PA from Maureen Fitzpatrick (fiddle), Brian Conway (fiddle), Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Andy McGann (fiddle), Joe Burke (accordion), Lori Cole (piano). Tape plays back too fast. (Length: 01:20:00), 1981 (Box 26, Item aiamm930C)
    - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival - Duets/Afternoon Concert - "Tape 3." Side A: Mike Rafferty and Jack Coen (flutes), John Kelly and Danny Flynn (Philadelphia Ceili Group musicians) play for dance demonstration; Side B: Concert performances by Joe and John Vesey (fiddles), Eileen Ivers (fiddle) and Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar). (Length: 01:00:00) Original tapes at American Folklife Center., 1981 (Box 26, Item aiamm931C)
    - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival - "Afternoon Concert - Tape 4." Performances by Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo, guitar) and Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Guilday and Roslyn Briley (harps), Martin and Brendan Mulvihill (fiddles) with Andy O'Brien (vocals, guitar). (Length: 00:50:00) Original tapes at American Folklife Center., 1981 (Box 26, Item aiamm932C)
    - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival - "Afternoon Concert - Tape 5." Performances by Touchstone, Dolores Keane (vocals), John Faulkner (guitar, vocals) and Eamon Curran (flute). (Length: 00:45:00) Original tapes at American Folklife Center., 1981 (Box 26, Item aiamm933C)
    - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival - "Evening Concert." Performances by teenaged Eileen Ivers (fiddle) and Joanie Madden (flute), Dolores Keane (vocals), John Faulkner (vocals, guitar) and Eamon Curran (flute). (Length: 01:00:00) Original tapes at American Folklife Center., 1981 (Box 26, Item aiamm934C)
    - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival - "Evening Concert." Performances by the Egan family including 12-year old Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Mark Simos (guitar), Tim Britton (uilleann pipes), Jack Coen and Mike Rafferty (flutes), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo) and Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) (Length: 01:00:00) Original tapes at American Folklife Center., 1981 (Box 26, Item aiamm935C)
    - "Blended Scotch - Knoxville." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], 1981 (Box 27, Item aiamm936C)
    - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival. "Tape 2 - Duets." Labeled "Mick this tape is shit." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], 1981 (Box 27, Item aiamm937C)
    - Radio Shows. Side A: Aidan O'Hara and Moloney discuss the six Long Note programs Moloney is about to host. (1/7/81) Side B: Moloney's third Long Note program profiling the Irish Tradition. (1/26/81) (Length: 01:30:00), Jan 7 & 26, 1981 (Box 26, Item aiamm1218C)
    - Long Note. "2nd Program." Radio show hosted by Moloney profiling Ed Reavy. (Length: 01:00:00), Jan 19, 1981 (Box 26, Item aiamm1217C)
    - Long Note. "4th Program." Radio show hosted by Moloney profiling Irish music in Philadelphia. (Length: 01:00:00), Feb 2, 1981 (Box 26, Item aiamm1219C)
    - Session at the Gandy Dancer, Baltimore, MD. Musicians include: Dessie Wilkinson (flute), Mick Moloney (mandolin, banjo), Unidentified (whistle, fiddle, dulcimer, guitar, accordion) (Length: 01:30:00), Jul 4, 1981 (Box 26, Item aiamm1212C)
    - "Boston Session. Seamus Connolly et al" [Needs significant preservation before digitization], Jul, 1981 (Box 27, Item aiamm1204C)
    - Milwaukee Session. Musicians include Liz Carroll (fiddle), Sean McGlynn (accordion), Mick Moloney (banjo), Kevin Burke (fiddle). [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], Aug, 1981 (Box 27, Item aiamm939C)
    - Long Note. Two episodes of Irish radio program hosted by Moloney. Side A: Palatines and Flanagan Brothers with Mike Flanagan interviews. Side B: Moloney retrospective with review of album, Strings Attached. (Length: 01:00:00), Feb 16, 1981 and Sep 3, 1981 (Box 26, Item aiamm938C)
    - Long Note. Irish radio program hosted by Moloney about the Irish recording industry in the US in the 1970s with profiles of Green Linnet and Shanachie including an interview with Shanachie co-founder Dan Collins. (Length: 01:00:00), Sep 2, 1981 (Box 26, Item aiamm940C)
    - "Gaelic Festival Cassette 1." Concert performance by Blended Scotch, Norman and Nancy Blake, Mick Moloney (banjo), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) in Knoxville, TN. (Length: 02:00:00), Oct 17, 1981 (Box 26, Item aiamm1215C)
    - "Gaelic Festival Cassette 2." Concert performance by Mick Moloney (banjo), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) with Blended Scotch. (Length: 00:40:00), Oct 17, 1981 (Box 26, Item aiamm1216C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance. (Length: 00:10:00), 1982 (Box 26, Item aiamm941C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance. Performers: Pueblo dancers with translators, Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:40:00), 1982 (Box 26, Item aiamm942C)
    - "People Around Here." Script for a slide show about life in southern Appalachia produced by Executive Director of the National Council for the Traditional Arts, Joe Wilson for the World’s Fair. (Length: 00:20:00), 1982 (Box 26, Item aiamm943C)
    - Long Note. Irish radio program about Irish music in America featuring Jackie Daly (accordion), Frankie Gavin (fiddle) entitled "Is Nostalgia the Thing of the Future?" (Length: 00:45:00), Jan 18, 1982 (Box 26, Item aiamm944C)
    - Session in Clarecastle. Musicians include: Denis Doody (accordion), Maeve Donnelly (fiddle), Mick Moloney (banjo), Pat Sky (uilleann pipes), Tim Lyons (vocals). [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], Jan, 1982 (Box 27, Item aiamm945C)
    - Session in Clarecastle. Pub session near Ennis, Co. Clare. Musicians include: Tim Lyons (vocals), Maeve Donnelly (fiddle), Patrick Sky (uilleann pipes), Mick Moloney (banjo), P. Gavin, Denis Doody (accordion), Casey. Includes recording of players leaving and getting into cars; Side B is very distorted recording of a car ride. (Length: 00:30:00), Jan, 1982 (Box 26, Item aiamm946C)
    - Session in Killarney. Quiet session with Moloney (banjo) and Mick Cronin (flute), brother of Johnny and Paddy Cronin. (Length: 00:45:00), Jul 18, 1982 (Box 26, Item aiamm947C)
    - Keane, Jimmy (accordion), Moloney, Mick (banjo), O'Connell, Robbie (guitar, vocals) Concert performance at the World's Fair, Knoxville, TN. [Needs significant preservation before digitization], Jul 29, 1982 (Box 27, Item aiamm1202C)
    - Milwaukee Session. Big session with Frankie Gavin (fiddle), Jackie Daly (accordion), Tim Lyons (vocals), Maeve Donnelly (fiddle), Denis Doody (accordion), Moloney (banjo), Pat Sky (uilleann pipes), Casey. (Length: 00:20:00), Aug, 1982 (Box 26, Item aiamm948C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance. "Tape 2." Concert performance in Sierra Leone Town Hall. (Length: 00:20:00), Oct 7, 1982 (Box 26, Item aiamm949C)
    - O'Connor, Mairtin (accordion), Moloney, Mick (banjo), Wilkinson, Dessie (flute) Moloney dictates ideas for a song followed by a kitchen session with some informal chat. (Length: 00:30:00), post 1982 (Box 26, Item aiamm950C)
    - Session and Recording Session at Jack Coen's. Session in the Bronx, NY with Mike Rafferty (flute), Sean McGlynn (accordion), Jack Coen (flute), Moloney (banjo); recording session featuring Coen, solo and with guitar accompaniment. (Length: 00:30:00), pre 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm951C)
    - "Moloney, O'Donnell, Carroll." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], 1983 (Box 27, Item aiamm952C)
    - "Mt. Airy 1983 - Banjo / Fiddle - Cocktail Party." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.] (Box 27, Item aiamm953C)
    - Session at 20 W. Harvey St. (Part 1) Musicians include: Jerry O’Sullivan (pipes), Timmy Britton (pipes), Mick Moloney (banjo), Mark Simos (fiddle, guitar), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Siobhan Egan (fiddle, whistle). (Length: 01:30:00), Jan 22, 1983 (Box 16, Item aiamm538R)
    - Session at 20 W. Harvey St. (Part 2) Musicians include: Jerry O’Sullivan (pipes), Timmy Britton (pipes), Mick Moloney (banjo), Mark Simos (fiddle, guitar), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Siobhan Egan (fiddle, whistle). (Length: 01:30:00), Jan 22, 1983 (Box 16, Item aiamm537R)
    - Morley's Pub. Side A: Concert performance by Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar), James Keane (accordion) in Norristown, PA; Side B: Commercial recording of Dubliners and a poor quality broadcast of the Wolf Trap Festival. (Length: 00:40:00), Feb, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm954C)
    - St. Paul Radio. Concert performance by Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo, guitar), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Tim Britton (uilleann pipes) broadcast on a Saturday afternoon folk show on WCAL - FM, 89.3 in Northfield, MN. (Length: 01:30:00), Mar 8, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm955C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Ambassador's Residence, Brazzaville, Congo. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:50:00), Sep 15, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm956C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Veg Theatre, Brazzaville, Congo. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:50:00), Sep 16, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm957C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Intercontinental Hotel, Kinshasa, Zaire. Tape 2. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:25:00), Sep 17, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm958C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Palais du Peuple, Kinshasa, Zaire. Tape 2. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:45:00), Sep 18, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm959C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Palais du Peuple, Kinshasa, Zaire - Tape 1. [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], Sep 18, 1983 (Box 27, Item aiamm960C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Veg Theatre, Brazzaville, Congo. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:50:00), Sep 19, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm961C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Palais du Peuple, Kinshasa, Zaire. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:20:00), Sep 19, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm962C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Abbia Theater, Cameroon, Tape 1. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:50:00), Sep 22, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm963C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Cameroon. Tape 1. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:50:00), Sep 24, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm964C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Bula, Cameroon. Tape 2. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:20:00), Sep 24, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm965C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Cameroon. Tape 1. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:50:00), Sep 25, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm966C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Abidjan, Ivory Coast. Tape 1. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:50:00), Sep 29, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm967C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Abidjan, Ivory Coast. Tape 2. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:50:00), Sep 29, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm968C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Town Hall, Freetown, Sierra Leone. Tape 1. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:30:00), Oct 2, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm969C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Daniel Sorano Theater, Dakar, Senegal. Tape 2. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:50:00), Oct 2, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm970C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Daniel Sorano Theater, Dakar, Senegal. Tape 1. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:50:00), Oct 2, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm971C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Ibi Mar Diop Stadium, Dakar, Senegal. Tape 2. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:30:00), Oct 4, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm972C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Ibi Mar Diop Stadium, Dakar, Senegal. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:50:00), Oct 4, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm973C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance. Moloney teaches a class on Irish song; short interview with his 5-year old son, Fintan. (Length: 00:40:00), Oct 4, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm974C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Mammy Yoko Hotel, Freetown, Sierra Leone. Tape 2. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:20:00), Oct 6, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm975C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Mammy Yoko Hotel, Freetown, Sierra Leone. Tape 1. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 01:00:00), Oct 6, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm976C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Mammy Yoko Hotel, Freetown, Sierra Leone. Tape 1. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 01:00:00), Oct 6, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm977C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Mammy Yoko Hotel, Freetown, Sierra Leone. Tape 2. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:30:00), Oct 8, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm978C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Monrovia Library, City Hall. Tape 1 of 1. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:45:00), Oct 11, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm979C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, Ambassador's Residence, Upper Volta. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:40:00), Oct 14, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm980C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, American Cultural Center, University of Oua…,Upper Volta. Tape 1 of 1. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:25:00), Oct 15, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm981C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, American Center, Upper Volta. Tape 1 of 1. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 01:00:00), Oct 15, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm982C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, University of Oua…, Upper Volta. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:45:00), Oct 17, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm983C)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, DCM's Residence, Upper Volta. Performers: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Donnie Golden (dance). (Length: 00:30:00), Oct 18, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm984C)
    - Green Fields of America. Concert performance at the 12th Gambier Folk Festival, Kenyon College, Gambier, OH. Musicians include: Mick Moloney (banjo, vocals), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Jimmy Keane (accordion), Donny Golden (dance). (Length: 01:00:00), Dec 29, 1983 (Box 26, Item aiamm985C)
    - Session in Philadelphia, PA. Musicians include: Paddy O'Brien (accordion), Seamus Egan (flute), Mick Moloney (banjo), Sean O'Driscoll. (Length: 00:10:00), 1984 (Box 26, Item aiamm986C)
    - "Weissman’s House Concert." Musicians: Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo), Robbie O’Connell (vocals, guitar), Jimmy Keane (accordion). [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], Jan 14, 1984 (Box 27, Item aiamm987C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo), O'Connell, Robbie (guitar), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Concert performance on their first tour. (Length: 00:45:00), Jan 23, 1984 (Box 26, Item aiamm988C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo), O'Connell, Robbie (guitar), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Concert performance. (Length: 01:00:00), Jan 23, 1984 (Box 26, Item aiamm989C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo), O'Connell, Robbie (guitar), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Second half of a concert performance in Tucson, AZ. (Length: 01:00:00), Feb 5, 1984 (Box 26, Item aiamm990C)
    - Mick Moloney and Friends. St. Patrick's Day concert performance at Georgetown University, Washington, D.C. Musicians include: Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo, guitar), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle). (Length:01:00:00), Mar 17, 1984 (Box 26, Item aiamm991C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo), O'Donnell, Eugene (fiddle) Concert performance at the Spoleto Festival, Charleston, S.C. (Part one of two) (Length: 01:30:00), Jun 2, 1984 (Box 26, Item aiamm992C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo), O'Donnell, Eugene (fiddle) Concert performance at the Spoleto Festival, Charleston, S.C. (Part two of two) (Length: 00:25:00), Jun 2, 1984 (Box 26, Item aiamm993C)
    - Sessions at Friel's. Pub sessions in Milltown Malbay, Co. Clare with Moloney, Noel Hill (concertina), Sean Keane (fiddle), Frankie Kennedy (flute). (Length: 01:30:00), Jul 1, 1984 (Box 26, Item aiamm994C)
    - "Banjo Examples Used at Miltown Lecture." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], Jul 1, 1984 (Box 27, Item aiamm995C)
    - Session at Conway's. Lively pub session in Milltown Malbay, Co. Clare with Moloney, fiddles and accordion. (Length: 00:55:00), Jul 3, 1984 (Box 26, Item aiamm996C)
    - Mulvihill, Martin (fiddle), Noisy session with Richard Casey, labeled "Athea." (Length: 00:10:00), Jul 24. 1984 (Box 26, Item aiamm997C)
    - Willie Clancy Week. Moloney lecture interspersed with musical examples in Miltown Malbay, Co. Clare recorded for the Long Note radio program, "Banjo Music." (Length: 00:45:00), Jul, 1984 (Box 26, Item aiamm998C)
    - "Sessions Miltown 1984." A variety of sessions featuring musicians Noel Hill (concertina), Tony Linnane (fiddle), Tony McMahon (accordion) in Miltown Malbay, Co. Clare and a private recording of Frank Harte singing several songs. (Length: 00:50:00), Jul, 1984 (Box 26, Item aiamm999C)
    - Green Fields of America. Second half of a concert performance. Musicians include: Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar), Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Jack Coen (flute), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina), Mick Moloney (guitar, vocals, banjo), James Keane (accordion), Liz Carroll (fiddle). Liz Carroll plays tunes for O'Sullivan at the end. (Length: 00:45:00), Oct 26, 1984 (Box 26, Item aiamm1000C)
    - Green Fields of America. Second half of a concert performance in Memphis, TN. Musicians include: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar), James Keane (accordion) (Length:01:00:00), Nov 3, 1984 (Box 26, Item aiamm1001C)
    - Green Fields of America. Concert performance in Nashville, TN. Musicians include: Mick Moloney (vocals, guitar, banjo), Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Jack Coen (flute), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina), Liz Carroll (fiddle), James Keane (accordion), Robbie O'Connell (guitar, vocals), Nov 4, 1984 (Box 26, Item aiamm1002C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo), Keane, Jimmy (accordion), Carroll, Liz (fiddle), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar) - End of an echoey concert performance in Laytonville, CA. (Length: 00:20:00), 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1039C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Brazzaville. (Length: 00:40:00), 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1033C)
    - "Mick et. al. - Tucson, AZ - 1st set." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], Feb 9, 1985 (Box 27, Item aiamm1003C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo), O'Donnell, Eugene (fiddle), O'Sullivan, Jerry (uilleann pipes),Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Muted, hissy concert performance at International House, Philadelphia, PA. (Length: 00:45:00), Mar 16, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1005C)
    - Mick Moloney and Friends. St. Patrick's week concert performance at International House, Philadelphia, PA. Musicians include: Mick Moloney (guitar, banjo, vocals), Jimmy Keane (accordion), Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes). (Length: 01:00:00), Mar, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1004C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Santo, Uruguay - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00), Apr 12, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1006C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Santo, Uruguay - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00), Apr 12, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1007C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Paysendu, Uruguay - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00), Apr 13, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1008C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Paysendu, Uruguay - "Tape 2." (Length: 00:45:00), Apr 13, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1009C)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance - Concert performance in Montevideo, Uruguay - "Tape 1." (Length: 00:45:00), Apr 15, 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1010C)